God's Country is a mystery, thriller, western film directed by Julian Higgins.
When a grieving college professor confronts two hunters she catches trespassing on her property,
she's drawn into an escalating battle of wills with catastrophic consequences.
Sandra Guidry, played by Thandiwe Newton.
Gus Wolf, played by Jeremy Bobb.
Samuel Cody, played by Jefferson White.
Nathan Cody, played by Joris Jarsky.
Gretchen, played by Tanaya Beatty.
Arthur Gates, played by Kai Lennox.
God's Country is a 2022 American thriller film co-written and directed by Julian
Higgins, based on the short story "Winter Light" by James Lee Burke.
The film stars Thandiwe Newton, Jeremy Bobb, Joris Jarsky,
Jefferson White, Kai Lennox, and Tanaya Beatty.
It had its world premiere in the Premieres section of the 38th Sundance Film Festival on January
23, 2022, and was released theatrically in United States on September 16, 2022.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.